{
    "1": [
      {
        "question": "Caesar was stabbed 21 times at the age of +55 (F24)",
        "answer": "F24"
      },
      {
        "question": "Another word for everything (A11)",
        "answer": "A11"
      },{
        "question": "Transpositions: 1,4,3,6,5,2,10,7,9,8 -> AWSREN4IYS (Y4)",
        "answer": "Y4"
      },{
        "question": "Substitution: Alphabet: Zyxwvutsrqponmlkjihgfedcba C.T: Gsv Zmhdvi rh I gdvmgb ulfi (L24)",
        "answer": "L24"
      },
      {
        "question": "G9+5 (L14)",
        "answer": "L14"
      },
      {
        "question": "NE (N5)",
        "answer": "N5"
      }

    ],
    "2": [
        {
            "question": "Caesar was stabbed 21 times at the age of +55 (F24)",
            "answer": "F24"
          },
          {
            "question": "Another word for everything (A11)",
            "answer": "A11"
          },{
            "question": "Transpositions: 1,4,3,6,5,2,10,7,9,8 -> AWSREN4IYS (Y4)",
            "answer": "Y4"
          },{
            "question": "Substitution: Alphabet: Zyxwvutsrqponmlkjihgfedcba C.T: Gsv Zmhdvi rh I gdvmgb ulfi (L24)",
            "answer": "L24"
          },
          {
            "question": "G9+5 (L14)",
            "answer": "L14"
          },
          {
            "question": "NE (N5)",
            "answer": "N5"
          }
    ]
  }